so I've learned more in these maths than
I have in all my years I'm a nerd I got
a PhD I learned more about life about
the mind that these masks that I have in
all the years of school and I think two
things two of the biggest things I took
away is the humbling reality that I'm
not special and if you want to be good
at anything you have to work really hard
and if you want to be the best in the
world at something like I do I want to
build robots better than anybody else in
the world or whether that's knitting or
yodeling anything you have to work but
York ever worked harder than anyone else
in the world and the second lesson I
learned I used to compete a lot they
lose a lot and he used to I used to hurt
to lose and I remember I don't know if
the remembers this conversation but I
think it leaked Bluebell I was going to
a big competition and I said you know I
don't know I'm gonna win it's like 15
people division and you said well give
everything you can to win but whether
you win or lose you're still gonna have
a home here I'm still gonna love you so
the two things I'd like to say thank you
for is the pain